<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2017 LasLabs Inc.
     License AGPL-3.0 or later (http://www.gnu.org/licenses/agpl). -->

<odoo noupdate="1">

    <record id="website_contract_template_default" model="account.analytic.contract.template">
        <field name="name">Default Template</field>
        <field name="website_description" type="xml">
            <section data-snippet-id="text-block">
                <section>
                    <h1 class="page-header">Contract</h1>
                    <p class="bg-danger">Disclaimer: This demo contract is not to be used for real business purposes.</p>
                    <p>
                        This Agreement is made to the start date of Date, between Client, having its principal place of Client Address
                        and Company, having its principal place of Company Address.
                        In consideration of Client retaining Company to perform support services for Client, it is agreed as follows:
                    </p>
                </section>
                <section>
                    <h3>Compensation and Term</h3>
                    <p>
                        Client hereby retains Company and Company hereby agrees to perform the following services: Consulting services of Company
                        as required by Client,through December 31, 20--. Company will at various times perform services at Client's headquarters,
                        at other Client facilities, or at Company facilities, as directed by Client. Company will perform the services at various
                        times and for various durations as directed by Client.
                    </p>
                    <h4>The following fees shall apply:</h4>
                    <p>
                        <strong>..........$X per hour for services.</strong>
                    </p>
                    <p>
                        Reasonable and necessary business and travel expenses actually incurred by Company shall be reimbursed by Client upon submission
                        of expense reports with back-up documentation. All such expenses and all travel plans must be approved in advance by Client.
                        Company shall provide detailed invoices and shall maintain, and provide, upon request, backup documentation for a period of
                        one year from the date of the respective invoices. Client shall make full payment for services within thirty days of invoice.
                        If Company brings a legal action to collect any sums due under this Agreement, it shall be entitled to collect, in addition
                        to all damages, its costs of collection, including reasonable attorney's fees. This Agreement shall commence on the date stated
                        above, and shall remain in effect until all obligations under this Agreement have been properly completed. Either party to this
                        Agreement may terminate this Agreement with or without cause by providing at least 21 days written notice to the other party.
                    </p>
                </section>
                <section>
                    <h5>Warranties by Company</h5>
                    <p>
                        Company represents and warrants to Client that it has the experience and ability to perform the services required by this
                        Agreement; that it will perform said services in a professional, competent and timely manner; that it has the power to enter into
                        and perform this Agreement; and that its performance of this Agreement shall not infringe upon or violate the rights of any third
                        party or violate any federal, provincial and municipal laws. Client shall provide requisite training for additional products or services
                        required by this Agreement which are not within Company's area of expertise.
                    </p>
                </section>
                <section>
                    <h3>Independent Contractor</h3>
                    <p>
                        Company acknowledges that the services rendered under this Agreement shall be solely as an independent contractor.
                        Company shall not enter into any contract or commitment on behalf of Client. Company further acknowledges that it is
                        not considered an affiliate or subsidiary of Client, and is not entitled to any Client employment rights or benefits. It is
                        expressly understood that this undertaking is not a joint venture.
                    </p>
                    <p>
                        Company recognizes and acknowledges that this Agreement creates a confidential relationship between Company and Client
                        and that information concerning Client's business affairs, customers, vendors, finances, properties, methods of operation, computer
                        programs, and documentation, and other such information, whether written, oral, or otherwise, is confidential in nature. All such
                        information concerning Client is hereinafter collectively referred to as "Confidential Information." Company agrees to follow
                        Client Information Security procedures and otherwise take all reasonable precautions for the protection of Confidential Information.
                    </p>
                </section>
                <section>
                    <h3>Non-Disclosure</h3>
                    <p>
                        Company agrees that, except as directed by Client, it will not at any time during or after the term of this Agreement disclose
                        any Confidential Information to any person whatsoever and that upon the termination of this Agreement it will turn over to Client
                        all documents, papers, and other matter in its possession or control that relate to Client. Company further agrees to bind its
                        employees and subcontractors to the terms and conditions of this Agreement.
                    </p>
                </section>
                <section>
                    <h3>Grant</h3>
                    <p>
                        Company agrees that its work product produced in the performance of this Agreement shall remain the exclusive property of Client, and
                        that it will not sell, transfer, publish, disclose or otherwise make the work product available to third parties without Client's prior
                        written consent. Any rights granted to Company under this Agreement shall not affect Client's exclusive ownership of the work product.
                    </p>
                </section>
                <section>
                    <h3>Office Rules</h3>
                    <p>
                        Company shall comply with all office rules and regulations, including security requirements, when on Client premises.
                    </p>
                </section>
                <section>
                    <h3>Conflict of Interest</h3>
                    <p>
                        Company shall not offer or give a gratuity of any type to any Client employee or agent.
                    </p>
                </section>
                <section>
                    <h3>Governing Law</h3>
                    <p>
                        This Agreement shall be construed and enforced in accordance with the laws of Governing Authority.
                    </p>
                </section>
                <section>
                    <h3>Entire Agreement and Notice</h3>
                    <p>
                        This Agreement contains the entire understanding of the parties and may not be amended without the specific written consent of both parties.
                        Any notice given under this Agreement shall be sufficient if it is in writing and if sent by certified or registered mail.
                    </p>
                </section>
            </section>
        </field>
    </record>

</odoo>
